Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory8 Mss.B.B61.inventory08
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents L
  - Lopatin, I.A. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - Curriculum vitae.
      - See Lopatin, I.A. to Sapir, E., Jan. 27, 1930.
    - I.A. Lopatin -- to E. Sapir, 1930 Jan. 27; 1p.
      (Enc: his curriculum vitae.)
  - López, José -- (see also Lónez, José) (Box 57)
    - From Boas, date?
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 10
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 4
  - Lopez Contreras (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 6; 1p.
  - Loram, C.T. (Box 57)
    - C.T. Loram -- to H.H. Bryan, 1933 Nov. 29; 2p.
  - Lord, L.E. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 24; 1p.
  - Lorentzen, C. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
  - Lorge, Irving (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p.
  - Lorimer, Frank (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 July 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 1; 1p.
    - F. Lorimer -- to O. Klineberg, 1933 Jan. 9; telegram
    - F. Lorimer -- to F. Osborn, 1938 Feb. 15; 2p.
  - Lorimer, G.H. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 12; 1p.
  - Lorwin, Val R. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p.
  - Loth (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar.; telegram
    - (Attached: Loth's reply., Mar. 23, 1923)
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 23; telegram
    - (Attached: Boas, F.'s telegram of Mar. 1923
  - Loubat, Joseph F., le Duc de (Box 57)
    - 1898 Dec. 1, 2p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Feb. 23; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1901 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1898 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1901 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 May 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1902 July 22; 3p.
    - J.F. Loubat -- to K. v.d. Steinen, 1902 Oct.; 3p.
  - Loubat Fund (Box 57)
    - See Boas, F. Memorandum..., Dec. 1940
  - Loubt? Jules (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1913 June 30; 2p.
  - Loud, Oliver S. (Box 57)
    - See Panth, Bhola D. Aug. 26, 1942., 1942 Nov. 6; 2p.
  - Loukotka, C. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 15; 1p.
  - Love, Fernando (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 28; 1p.
  - Lovejoy, Arthur O. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - See Wiener, Philip Paul, Nov. 30, 1938.
  - Lovestone, J. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 2; 2p.
    - (Enc: List), 1933 May 5; 1p.
    - (Enc: List), 1933 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 21; 1p.
  - Lovett, R.M. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 26; 1p.
  - Low, Seth (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1899 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - (See letter dated Nov. 10, 1908 to Butler, Nicholas Murray), 1911 July 29
    - To Boas, 1896 May 5
    - To Boas, 1896 May 7
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 May 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
    - S. Low -- to Dr. A. Jacobi, 1892 Sept. 7; 1p.
  - Lowdermilk, W.H. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 17; 1p.
  - Lowe, Donald V. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1942 Aug. 10; 1p.
  - Lowe, J.T.C. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 18; 1p.
  - Lowell, Augustus Lawrence (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1910 June 25
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p.
      (Enc: List of publications desired.)
    - To Boas, 1910 May 26
    - To Boas, 1910 June 8
    - To Boas, 1910 July 5
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
    - A.L. Lowell -- to R.B. Dixon, 1910 Dec. 17
    - A.L. Lowell -- from F.W. Putnam, 1897 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1898 Apr. 8
  - Lowenberg, E. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - (Enc: American Community. Committee. Minutes of Nov. 15 & 25 1929 Preliminary survey of Centerville. Report. Form letter Conference of executives of Peace movement. Form letter Research problems of educating communities in international affairs.), 1930 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - (Enc: American Community. Minutes of 6th meeting Jan. 10, 1930, 1930 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 3; 32p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 4; 1p.
  - Lowenstein, S. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 3
  - Lowenthal, Marvin (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 27; 1p.
  - Lowi, J. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1935 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 1; 1p.
  - Löwi, Moritz (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 12; 1p.
  - Lowie, Robert H. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1905 Sept. 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1915 Sept. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 3; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 16; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 8; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 13; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 June 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct.; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 June 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 25
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 July 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 12; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1916 July 9; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 2; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 July 31
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 July 26; postcard
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 May 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Sept. 29; 3p.
    - (Enc: 2 notes), 1929 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 30; telegram
    - See Boas, F. to Woodworth, R.S., Sept. 2, 1931.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 June 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 3; 4p.
    - (Enc. with Lowie, R.H. Oct. 4, 1935., 1935 Oct. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 31; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - R.H. Lowie -- from F.H. Allport, 1913 Nov. 21
  - Lowman, C.L. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1919 July 13; 1p.
      (Enc: Lowman, C.L. to Smithsonian Institution. Bureau of Anthropology. Dir.
    - C.L. Lowman -- to Smithsonian Institution, 1919 July 12; 2p.
  - Lowman, G.S. Jr. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 May 24; 2p.
  - Lowthermilk (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 6; 1p.
  - Lubarsky, David A. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 June 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 14
  - Lübeck, Germany (Box 57)
    - Boas, F. -- to Hansischer Geschichtsverein, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p.
  - Lubin, S.J. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 4; 1p.
  - Lucas, F.A. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 28; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 10; (16?)
    - From Boas, 1913 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 13
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc: Letter to Tower, R.W. from Brill, E.J. Leiden, Aug. 13, 1920. Draft of agreement of Amer. Museum of Natural History and Brill.), 1920 Oct. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - (Enc: Revised Draft of agreement with Brill for the Jesup North Pacific Publications), 1920 Oct. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - F.A. Lucas -- to P.E. Goddard, 1914 Mar. 23; 2p.
    - F.A. Lucas -- from W. Jochelson, 1913 Mar. 20
    - F.A. Lucas -- to W. Jochelson, 1913 Apr. 1
    - (Enc. with Lucas, F.A. Apr. 1, 1913, 1913 Dec. 28
  - Luccock, Halford E. (Box 57)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938.
  - Luchaire, Julien (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - J. Luchaire -- to Institut international de Coopération intellectuale, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - (Attached: Schrijnen, J. to Luchaire, J. Dec. 14, 1928, 1928 Dec. 3; 2p.
    - J. Luchaire -- from J. Schrijnen, 1928 Dec. 14
  - Luchin (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1908 July 17
    - To Boas, 1908 July 24; postcard
    - To Boas, 1908 July 29
  - Lucht, H. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 14; 2p.
  - Lucké, B. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 2; 1p.
  - Luckey, J. C. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1890 June 7
  - Lüdemann, Carl (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 9; 1p.
  - Ludenadel, C.W. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 16; 3p.
  - Ludendorff, von (Box 57)
    - See Fasting, G. to Ludendorff, von, Mar. 2, 1925.
    - From Fasting, G., Jan. 16, 1925.
    - (Enc. with Fasting, G. to Ludendorff, von, Mar. 2, 1925)
  - Ludwig, E.J. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 4; 1p.
  - Luebbert, C.W.H. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 6; 1p.
  - Luedecke, L. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1923 Nov. 5; 2p.
  - Lüders, Heinrich (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1922 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Mar. 11; 1p.
  - LüdtkensGerhart (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p.
  - , Lulie, 1907 Apr 22 (Box 57)
  - Lumholtz, Carl (Box 57)
    - C. Lumholtz -- to Mrs. de Forest, 1903 Aug. 1; 8p.
  - Lumley, F.E. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 18; 1p.
  - Lund, J.J. (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 11
  - Lunn, Arnold (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 6; 2p.
  - Lurie, H.L. (Box 57)
    - To Boas, 1933 May 10; 1p.
  - Luschan, Emma von (Box 57)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 11; postcard
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 14; postcard
    - To Boas, 1926 May 30; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 1; postcard
    - To Boas, 1930 July 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 27; postcard
    - To Boas, 1930 July 27; postcard
  - Luschan, Felix von (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 21
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 3; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 31; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 5; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 13
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 20; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 20; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 13; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Aug. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1886 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1895 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 1; postcard
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 10; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1898 July 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1905 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 2; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 July 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 July 24
    - To Boas, 1908 July 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 May 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 July 3
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 9; postcard
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 29; postcard
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1915 May 19
    - To Boas, 1915 June 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 18; 12p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 22; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - (Enc: gruyter, Walter de to Seler, E. Mar. 11, 1920 2p.), 1920 Mar. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 6; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 July 1; postcard
    - To Boas, 1921 Aug. 19; postcard
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 7; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 21; postcard
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 27; postcard
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 28; postcard
    - To Boas, 1923 June 29; postcard
    - To Boas, 1923 July 8; postcard
    - To Boas, 1923 July 12; postcard
    - To Boas, 1923 Sept. 16; postcard
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 26; 2p.
  - Lusk, Graham (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 26; 1p.
  - Luthan, Antonio (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 4; 1p.
  - Luther, H. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 27; 1p.
  - Lutman, B.F. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 31; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1926 June 7; 1p.
  - Lutos? Miguel W. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 20; 1p.
  - Lutz, Frank E. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 20; postcard
  - Luzac & co. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 23
  - Lydenberg, H.M. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 19; 1p.
  - Lyman, Eugene W. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas
      - On margin of Boas, F. to Lyman, Eugene W., Oct. 24, 1941.
  - Lynch, David (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 5; 2p.
  - Lynch, Mrs. Jennie F. (?) (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 25; 3p.
  - Lynd, Mrs. Helen Merrell (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 18; 2p.
  - Lynd, Robert S. (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 July 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Rautenstrauch, W., Dec. 22, 1941.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 June 29; 1p.
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas Feb. 11, 1937., 1937 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 21; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938.
    - See Boas, F. to Villard, O.G. May 23, 1939., 1939 Dec.
    - See Boas, F. to Carlson, A.J. May 24, 1940., 1940 Dec. 18; 2p.
    - R.S. Lynd -- to H. Gaston-Heye, 1940 Dec.; 1p.
  - Lyon, E.P. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 18
  - Lyons, Daniel M. (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 17; 1p.
  - Lyons, Eugene (Box 58)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p.
  - Lyons, Muriel (Box 58)
    - To Boas, 1935 May 1; 1p.